makemoney.ng 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - MakeMoney

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://www.makemoney.ng.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

[Articles](https://www.makemoney.ng/category/articles/) on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

We will never share your personal information with third parties unless required by law.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our [business](https://www.makemoney.ng/tag/business/) activities such as offering customer service, sending email or advertising soultions. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.  And you can unsubscribe and erase your data from our newsletter at any point.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Contact information

On the off chance that you require any more data or have any inquiries regarding our privacy policy, please don’t hesitate to reach us by email at admin@makemoney.ng

## Additional information

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as an outsider seller, utilizes cookies to serve promotions on MakeMoney.ng.

.:: Google’s utilization of the DART treat empowers it to serve promotions to clients in light of their visit to MakeMoney.ng and different locales on the Internet.

.:: Users may quit the utilization of the DART treat by going by the Google advertisement and substance arrange privacy policy at the accompanying URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

A portion of our promoting accomplices may utilize cookies and web reference points on our webpage. Our publicizing accomplices incorporate … .

These outsider promotion servers or advertisement systems utilize innovation to the advertisements and connections that show up on MakeMoney.ng send specifically to your programs. They naturally get your IP address when this happens. Different advancements (, for example, cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may likewise be utilized by the outsider promotion systems to quantify the viability of their advertisements and/or to customize the publicizing content that you see.

MakeMoney.ng has no entrance to or control over these cookies that are utilized by outsider sponsors.

You advised to consult the separate privacy approaches of these outsider advertisement servers for more point by point data on their practices and for guidelines about how to quit certain practices. MakeMoney.ng’s privacy policy does not make a difference to, and we can’t control the exercises of, such different sponsors or sites.

On the off chance that you wish to debilitate cookies, you may do as such through your individual program alternatives. More nitty gritty data about treat administration with particular web programs can be found at the programs’ separate sites.

### Your continue usage of our website means you have agreed to this policy.
